Spirits, how do we deal with trans-spatial lifeforms that cause disasters?
Strategy 1, destroy them through overwhelming military force.
Or Strategy 2, date them and make them fall in love.
Strategy 2, date them and make them fall in love.
Comments open再見 2, date them and make them fall out in love.
न換 richter time switch.
It's pretty simple, Miss Okamine.
Yes, I am totally a boy now.
So I can stay in the same room as Shido when we go on the school trip.
I don't think so.
You can keep wearing those clothes, but it doesn't change the fact that boys and girls have to stay in separate rooms.
Excuse me.
I think you should approve Toka's unusual request.
Or at least consider it.
Huh?
Hold on.
What are you after?
I really admire that you have the courage to come out in front of everyone.
I think you deserve to stay in the boys' room, no question.
Look, I'm not saying thanks.
None needed.
Stop wasting time! The issue is not negotiable!
But it is still pretty uncommon for a girl to want to become a boy.
To keep things balanced will make Shido into a girl.
That literally makes no sense.
Then we can bathe together, tastefully.
How's that tasteful?
Wait a sec!
If he becomes a girl, he won't be able to stay in the boys' room with me!
You're a man now. You need to stay strong.
Then this must have been part of your plan all along!
You are both being ridiculous!
Boys and girls will be in separate rooms and no more gender swapping, got it?
Um, well, putting room assignments aside, you can choose your seats for the plane ride.
You can spend time together there!
The location for the school trip?
Yeah, Shido told me about it.
They were going to Okinawa, but now it's a Ruby Island.
We're talking a last-minute change here.
It seems a certain travel agency said they would cover all expenses in order to get publicity shots.
With all financial burden lifted, the school quickly agreed.
However...
Sounds suspicious.
Perhaps I'm reading too much into it.
But the agency Cross Travel?
It's a subsidiary of DEM Industries.
This was her game from the beginning, wasn't it?
You tricked me into the seat furthest from the window!
I won't be fooled again!
You never specified which seat you wanted.
Look, Shido.
I'm sorry.
You can see the horizon.
Super sorry.
Shido!
Triple sorry!
This sight is amazing, too!
Everybody knows the aisle is where the action is!
It's pretty cool.
The clouds look just like a carpet.
Well, if you like carpet, I've got what you want!
Right here!
Look at it, Shido!
If I pretend to nap, maybe they'll stop.
Pardon the candid camera.
But I had to capture such a priceless expression.
Uh, uh-huh.
Shido, who was that?
The teacher introduced her to us earlier.
She's the pro photographer the travel agency sent along with us.
A spirit.
Princess.
Your camera is making me jelly!
It's top of the line!
Must have cost thousands!
That's so lame!
You'd have to drive auto-focus!
Is that like a focal point shutter?
Gentlemen, please put your seats and tray tables in an upright and locked position and prepare for landing.
Wow!
No way!
Is that the ocean?
Yeah, I guess this is your first time to see it.
Uh-huh!
The water park we went to with Yoshino and Kotori was amazing!
But this place is even better!
More than you know.
Is something wrong?
God, I feel like someone's watching us.
We'll have them take our luggage to the hotel first, understood?
It was probably just the camera.
Incoming from Adeptus One.
They've reached Arubi Island.
Target confirmed.
Akaru Airport, North District.
Camera number six.
It's Princess, sir.
We found her.
That was anticlimactic.
The girl doesn't look like a spirit.
You must not let your guard down.
Intelligence indicates that she is a spirit.
That alone is reason enough to be on level one alert.
Roger that.
Set alert to level one.
By the way, aren't we supposed to have a wizard on the ground?
All right, class four.
Gather round!
That would be me.
We met earlier.
I'll report back to you later on, but for now, the kids are on the move.
Right!
Come on!
Eyes forward, class four!
Since this is a school trip, we'll start the learning now.
We're heading to the Arubi Island Records office.
How exciting!
Seriously?
It sounds like stupid boring.
Not so lame.
Hey, get it out of the way now.
Have fun later.
Am I right, sexy beast?
Okay, gang.
Everyone, follow the flag!
It's time.
Come on, let's book it.
But I know someone's been spying on us.
Hang on, Toka!
Aw, man!
Adeptus One to Arbitel.
Princess has broken off from the group.
Track her movements for me.
Also, activate Ashcroft Beta and set to standby.
Then cut off the island from outside communication.
Be ready to strike at any time.
Hey, you're gonna get left behind.
Shouldn't you be taking pictures of us?
So what?
Did you just come for some photos of the scenery?
That's so lame.
No, that's not it at all!
We got it already!
You're working, Ellen!
Being a field agent can be rough.
But these precautions seem a bit extreme.
Spirit or not, she's just a teenage girl.
Once we introduce her to the Bandersnatch Unit,
capturing her will be child's play.
Captain, we've got a problem.
The hell?
Weird, this weather came out of nowhere!
Look, if we don't get out of this storm,
it could get really bad!
Sorry, I ran off.
But I know someone was watching us!
I could feel it!
I bet it was just the locals giving a bunch of annoying students
the stink eye.
Now, which way to the records office?
What's going on?
This came to a head way too quickly!
Shido!
Get down!
Toka!
Taka!
Are you okay?
Uh...
Just my luck.
A spirit? Or the AST?
But the spatial quake alarm never sounded.
Spirits? Two of them?
I can't believe you! Please choose me, darling!
It doesn't matter! Yes, it does!
Well, I'll be going then. This isn't exactly the best timing for a meeting at HQ.
But it's a rare chance for the rounds to meet up in person, so I'm expected to make an appearance.
Go. You may leave it to me, Commander.
Don't worry. You can trust us to hold down the port.
Just promise that you'll hurry back when you're done.
But lo, the unbridled passion of youth set free during a school trip.
And I, Kyohei Kanazuki, will chronicle this page of Shido's salad days with every juicy detail during your absence.
Right. I reiterate. Please hurry back.
Sure. I'll try.
Okay. As acting commander of the mighty Frexinus, flood a course for 15,000 feet above the island.
Not too bad, Yuzuru.
Although I expected as much from my other half.
Too bad it will all have been in vain.
Rebuttal. Much has been learned from our 99 battles.
The advantage is clearly mine.
Such sad prattle.
We both know the only spirit even suitable to be Yamai's successor is me.
Negative. I am the one who will persevere.
The name Yamai does not fit one as lowly as you.
Your words are hollow. My future devil side has already shown me the inevitable end.
It gave me a vision of you, Yuzuru, impaled and dying on the end of my Sturm Lanza.
Refute. Your devil side has never been accurate in the slightest.
Shut up! It has so worked before! And don't you dare make fun of me!
Shin, can you hear me?
Reina?
Good. I finally got through.
Where are you in Toka currently?
Um, not sure.
Request. Kaguya, please provide information regarding the combat capabilities of your Sturm Lanza.
Ha! The very font of language dries up trying to describe the scope of its awesome power.
Tangible yet intangible. Visible yet unseen.
Only able to sate its thirst with stabbing and piercing.
Summary. Just like you, it is devoid of meaning.
That's not true! It does have meaning!
Maybe you're just too stupid to really understand!
Derisive. Your Sturm Lanza is laughable.
Huh. How dare you!
To punish you for such insolence, perhaps I should rip that smirk off your face right here and now!
We're gonna get caught in the middle!
Stink into darkness!
Torque. Hi-ya!
Stomp-a!
Huh?
Wait, is that a human?
Wondrous. I cannot suppress my surprise.
Uh, hi?
Why have you brought our sacred duel to a standstill, human? And what are your intentions for us?
Depending on your answer, I'll, uh, turn your body into a jelly with my shot in Lanza!
Discrepancy. Your weapon's name has changed completely.
Unimportant! Now be quiet already!
Query, since you are the one who was confused, why must I be quiet?
At this rate, we won't resolve anything. Unless...
I think I know how we can settle things. For good.
Question. What did you have in mind?
A new trial. We've had many contests, haven't we?
We've each had 25 victories and come to a draw 49 times. The list of events to compete in is rapidly dwindling.
However, there is still one competition which hasn't yet determined a victor between us.
Doubtful. Explain.
Hm.
Huh?
Hey, uh, we're back.
There's no denying. I'm obviously more lively and charming than she is.
Seduction. I'm more fully developed.
What gives?
Their transfer students.
This is highly unorthodox. The school never informed me they were coming.
It was so sudden, they were probably worried that they couldn't contact you in time.
Don't worry about the new girls. Leave them to me, okay?
Please focus your energy on the other students.
Oh, thank you.
So, Shido, all you have to do is make a simple little choice.
Just say, Kaguya, you drive me wild. Let me give myself to you, body and soul, forever.
Wrong. Kaguya is a poor choice. She is quite needy and childish. However, I would strongly recommend me.
Feeling a little smothered, are we?
Yeah.
Putting our feminine wiles to the test. We haven't tried that yet. Surely the true heir of the hurricane child, Yamai, would possess enough grace and charm to make all of creation quake in jealousy.
Reply, I believe I follow your logic. In truth, it may be the only attribute which we have not put to a competition.
Yuzuru, do you agree to pit our beauty against one another? Of course, my victory is certain.
Negative. There is no chance that you could ever beat me. After all, I am the cutest. To be frank, your looks are average at best.
What do you mean by that? It doesn't matter. This will be our decisive battle. Whoever gets this man to fall in love first will be the winner.
Come on now, handsome. Just spit it out. Which of us has more feminine charm, me or little miss boring there?
Question. Do you prefer a beautiful woman or a cheap floozy like her?
Look, I'm not a floozy. You take that back right now.
No, I am prettier than that trollop, Kaguya.
Stop! That's even worse!
Would everyone shut up for five seconds, please?
Let me ask you something first. Why are you ladies trying to duel each other for the hundredth time anyway?
Uh, oh, did we not mention that already?
Apologies. We forgot to tell you. As the arbitrator, you have the right to know all of the pertinent details.
You see, Kaguya and I were once combined as a single spirit.
The name of the spirit was Yamai.
Just pick me!
No, you have to choose me!
So, basically, for reasons yet to be announced, someday soon you'll both have to go back to being a single spirit.
And when that happens, the two different personalities won't be able to coexist. Is that right?
Correct. The personality of the original Yamai was lost ages ago.
Thus, Yuzuru or I will become the new Yamai, for there can be only one.
Correct. Explanation. In order to determine who that will be, we have fought tooth and nail for many years.
Fist fight. Foot race. Kendama. Eating contest. We competed in a variety of ways.
Those last two were way less dramatic.
What happens to the personality that loses?
It will cease to exist.
No way!
We really appreciate you, Shido. Thanks to you, we can compete in a way we've never been able to.
Affirmative. I have no objections if this matches what makes the final decision.
That can't be good.
Is there some kind of problem?
Yes. Fraxinus hasn't sent any updates or status reports in hours.
The reason is unknown, but I will investigate.
Anyway. And now, ladies, if you would both follow me, please.
Shin is more wily than he looks. I'll give you some tips to deal with him.
Well, that's just great. Two new spirits pop up and Reyna and I have to fly solo.
What kind of tips is she giving for them to deal with me?
Ah! Oh, hi, girls!
Shido, I give you permission to cleanse the impurities that have accumulated on your puny mortal body.
Confirmation. Please feel free to enter the bath.
Okay.
Hey, what made you think it was all right to take a bath with me?
Duh. How else am I going to make you go crazy for my pixie-like feminine charms?
Scornful. Feminine charms, you say?
Were you planning to buy some here because you didn't bring any with you, sister?
I swear I'll make you pay for that later, you cow!
Accepted. Now bring it on.
Excuse me! This is the men's bath!
Which means neither of you are even supposed to be on this side!
Better prepare yourself, stud.
I'll make you realize that you can never be satisfied by anyone but me.
Negative. Just think. There's only a flimsy white towel separating our flesh.
Yelp! Joystick! Come on!
Here we go. Ready?
Out of the kindness of my heart, you can have the first seduction attempt.
Negative. Not needed. However, you could use any handicap you can get, I'd wager.
Then the gloves are off.
The moment I make my big move, Shido's eyes will never stray from me again.
I just wanted to be charitable and let you have a glimmer of hope.
Skeptical. You have no idea what it takes to seduce a young man, do you?
You bet I do!
I'm super foxy!
Plus, I've got a ton of sexy techniques that a boy like you couldn't dream up in a million years!
Doubtful. Care to demonstrate?
All right. Just you watch.
Ah. How do you like that?
Uh... I'm confused.
Uh...
Hey! What are you laughing at?
Derision. Just as expected, your feminine charms leave something to be desired.
What did you say?
As if a girl without a shred of passion would have even the foggiest notion!
Falsehood. My worth would still be better than you.
Why don't you show us how it's done?
Accepted.
Here we go.
Hi, handsome.
Uh, thanks.
Wow! You sure showed me!
Can't believe you had me worried.
Live it.
I am not interested in your opinion.
Same here.
Noted. Your childish figure is not as effective at seduction as my womanly curves.
Nonsense! You know that we're identical!
Rebuttal.
Even if the measurements are the same, they feel completely different.
You're underestimating the attractiveness of a slender body.
Body. Slender body, you say?
Change the words to sound better all you wish, but you cannot alter the sad truth.
Are you seriously bragging because you have more fat on your chest?
Indignant. These breasts are pristine, but your jealousy is ugly.
And who's jealous of you, cow? I'm not, you understand me?
Shito thinks I'm cuter than some fatty like you any day of the week, no ifs, ands, or buts.
Wrong. When attempting to appeal to men, being flat-chested is a bad thing.
Chicken bones like yours wouldn't rate a second glance.
They aren't chicken bones!
Riposte. Don't ever call me a fatty.
You have more split-ins than I do!
Snark, you're smellier than I am whenever you get sweaty.
Oh? Well, you have more body fat than I do!
Pity. You're not intelligent enough to find another fault of mine to comment on.
Puffity fatty fat puffball!
Counter. Flat as a board flattened stein.
Hold on! The others might show up at any time!
It won't look good if you're caught in the men's bath!
Ha! What are you talking about, Shito?
Confirmed. There's no need to worry.
Uh, but why?
I love being first in the bath.
Hey! What are you thinking, being in a place like this?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
What are you doing in the men's bathing area?
What are you talking about?
I went in the room with a red sign, just like everybody told me to!
Huh? And how'd that happen?
Well, we might have switched the signs right before you came in.
Supplement. Once you came in, we put them back.
Like we would sink so low to use the men's bath.
Figures.
I got here early to be the first in the bath, but now I'm the fourth.
Uh, my mistake. I kind of got tricked. I'll get out right now.
Oh!
Second, Al, the ocean is like right there.
We would never get a view this good at home.
That's so lame.
Gotta make a plan. And quickly.
Shito, I'll obstruct their view.
You can hide behind me, then try to run away.
You sure?
Those girls tricked you into coming into the wrong bath.
So I'm gonna get you out.
Thank you.
I owe you one.
Hey!
Toph, I didn't tell you were here.
Don't hide over in the corner. Come and join us.
OMG, you have, like, perfect skin.
Balloon!
Something wrong?
No! No! Everything's fine!
Look!
Is that a giant piece of keto-tops in the sky?
What?
Wait, what the hell?
Are you feeling okay?
You just have to look up and away from me!
Look at me!
That way!
Isn't it a little early to sneak into a woman's bedroom?
We were delayed by unexpected circumstances.
But we will strike tonight.
Have Bandersnatch standing by and ready to move.
You chose me over my sister?
It doesn't really matter, does it?
Yoshido.
So...
Yes?
They gave us a lot of free time on this school trip.
That was, that was, the absolute journey
君を救う勇者の物語
アルオトヒノクに旅立つは勇者 桃源駆け抜け 目指すはお姫様
真っ暗な洞窟 風吹き荒れる山 凍ってく剣をかざして
瞳に映る勇気の炎 闇の手を振り払い 君の手を握く
今だって夢だって剣を手に 君のこと見つけるよ闇を裂いて
倒れたって暗くたって負けないから この手をきっと捕まえて
消えない雪の炎が 都会照らしている
君の手を振り払い 君の手を振り払い
今日がマグルザレタが到来
君の手を振り払い 君の手を振り払い 君の手を振り払い